{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","address":"7724 Fourteenth St","zipcode":"48206","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","licenseNumber":"034897","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/15/2017","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E610000004C7BBDC2DC654C0D035F7BDF12E4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44276","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","inspectionDate":"2018-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44276","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"inspectionid":"44276","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Routine inspections","subItem":"of premises for evidence of pests","problemDescription":"Not performed","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Inspections must be performed as stated above."}]},{"inspectionid":"42251","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","inspectionDate":"2018-05-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"112","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42251","inspectionDate":"5/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"42251","inspectionDate":"5/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"inspectionid":"42251","inspectionDate":"5/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Routine inspections","subItem":"of premises for evidence of pests","problemDescription":"Not performed","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Inspections must be performed as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"42251","inspectionDate":"5/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"42251","inspectionDate":"5/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"40396","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","inspectionDate":"2017-09-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"40672","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","inspectionDate":"2017-06-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40672","inspectionDate":"6/20/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Three compartment sink","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"inspectionid":"40672","inspectionDate":"6/20/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"40672","inspectionDate":"6/20/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Knowledge is to be obtained through an approved training program"}]},{"inspectionid":"38157","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","inspectionDate":"2017-03-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"36900","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","inspectionDate":"2016-10-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36900","inspectionDate":"10/26/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","violationCode":"6-501.112","violationDescription":"Dead or trapped birds, insects, rodents, and other pests shall be removed from control devices and the PREMISES at a frequency that prevents their accumulation,  decomposition, or the attraction of pests.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dead/trapped pest(s)","subItem":"rodents mice","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Pest droppings","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"865"}}